Guide to the Fern and Hersh Cohen Print Collection 1891-1948 PR 466
New-York Historical Society
Fern and Hersh Cohen Print Collection
1891-1948
New-York Historical Society
Cohen, Herschel
Cohen, Fern
PR 466
10 Linear feet in 27 folders
Approximately 200 works on paper by American artists, dating from 1891-1948, from the collection of Fern and Hersh Cohen. The majority of the prints depict various aspects of Depression era American life.
Arrangement
The prints are listed alphabetically by artist.
Biographical / Historical
The prints in this collection were amassed over a period of more than 40 years by Hersh Cohen, an investment manager, and his wife Fern Cohen, a school librarian. The Cohens have focused on collecting prints by American artists created between 1900 and World War II, with an emphasis on the Depression era.
A number of the prints were created under the auspices of the Works Progress Administration (WPA, renamed the Work Projects Administration in 1939), a New Deal government agency created by President Roosevelt that hired millions of Americans to execute public works and community service projects. While many WPA workers built roads, bridges, and other infrastructure, some divisions assigned people to work in the arts. The WPA Federal Art Project (FAP) was established in 1935 to create employment for artists during the Great Depression. The Graphic Arts Division of the program, which emphasized block printing and lithography, among other printmaking techniques, employed more than 700 artists across 36 American cities, many of whom used their work to address social justice issues.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Fern and Hersh Cohen, 2023.
Scope and Contents
This collection comprises approximately 200 works on paper by American artists, dating from 1891-1948. The majority of the prints depict facets of American life during the era of the Great Depression, a time of social upheaval and economic hardship for many. Included are scenes of workers at their jobs; strikes; homelessness; as well as people gathered on stoops, in bars, and at various amusements. Many of the prints are New York City views.
The container list includes the artist and title of all prints in the collection. Scope notes include information about printmaking technique and dimensions, as well as the presence of a WPA stamp. Dates, titles, and dimensions are based on information received from the donors.
Art, American -- 20th century; Depressions--1929--United States--Pictorial works.; Printmakers.; Aquatints (prints); Drypoints (prints); Etchings (prints); Linocuts.; Lithographs.; Wood engravings.; Woodcuts (prints); Cohen, Herschel; Cohen, Fern; United States. Works Progress Administration
- Abelman, Ida York - Consumers, 1939 (Folder FF 17)
  Scope and Contents
  Lithograph, 14 3/4" x 11 3/4", WPA.
- Anchel, Harold - Summer Afternoon, circa 1930 (Folder FF 15)
  Lithograph, 13" x 10", WPA.
- Anchel, Harold - News, undated (Folder FF 15)
  Lithograph, 11 13/16" x 9 5/16", WPA.
- Anchel, Harold - Folk Dance, undated (Folder FF 15)
  Lithograph, 10 3/8" x 11 3/4", WPA.
- Anchel, Harold - Bargain Sale, undated (Folder FF 15)
  Lithograph, WPA.
- Anchel, Harold - Subway, undated (Folder FF 23)
  Lithograph, WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Anderson, Carlos - Holiday Travelers, circa 1936-1942 (Folder FF 27)
  Lithograph, unmarked WPA.
- Arms, John Taylor - American Cathedral (The Woolworth Building), 1921 (Folder FF 4)
  Etching, 17 1/2" x 6 3/4".
- Bacon, Peggy - Tired Eyes, 1936 (Folder FF 20)
  Drypoint.
- Barlow, Lou - Night in the Park, circa 1938 (Folder FF 20)
  Wood engraving, WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Barlow, Lou - East River, circa 1939 (Folder FF 20)
  Wood engraving, Federal Art Project (NYC) WPA.
- Barr, Norman - Flophouse, 1939 (Folder FF 2)
  Lithograph, 9 3/4" x 12".
- Beccard, Helen Louise - Celebration in Central City [Crowded Street], 1937 (Folder FF 4)
  Lithograph, 14 1/2" x 11 5/6".
- Bell, Cecil C. - [Busy Street Stoops], 1933 (Folder FF 3)
  Etching, 7 7/8" x 9 7/8".
- Bendiner, Alfred - And So I Give You...Republican Convention Dewey Nominated, 1948 (Folder FF 20)
  Lithograph.
- Bendiner, Alfred - The Heroes of the Homefront (the Filter Room of the Aircraft Warning Service), circa 1943 (Folder FF 23)
- Besedick, Frank - Impressions, 1935-1939 (Folder FF 16)
  Wood engraving, WPA.
- Bird, Esther Brock - Times Square, 1934 (Folder FF 19)
- Bird, Esther Brock - The St. Moritz, 1934 (Folder FF 19)
- Bird, Esther Brock - Judson Memorial (Washington Square Park, NY), 1937 (Folder FF 19)
- Blanchard, Pablo - Uptown, undated (Folder FF 20)
  Woodcut.
- Blumenshein, Helen - Dusk, 1944 (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 13 3/6" x 8 13/16".
- Bohrod, Aaron - Washington Market, N.Y., 1931 (Folder FF 25)
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Theatre, 1931 (Folder FF 15)
  Etching, 3 1/16" x 2 1/16", WPA.
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Butcher, 1933 (Folder FF 15)
  Aquatint, 11 3/4" x 8 7/8", WPA.
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Bull Fiddle, 1939 (Folder FF 15)
  Etching, 11 3/4 x 8 7/8", WPA.
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Light Houskeeping, 1941 (Folder FF 15)
  Lithograph, 11 3/8" x 15 1/4".
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Riverfront, undated (Folder FF 15)
  WPA.
- Botts, Hugh Pearce - Street Musicians, circa 1936 (Folder FF 26)
  Etching, WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Brandfield, Dayton - Fulton Fish Market, undated (Folder FF 17)
  Lithograph, 16 1/2" x 13".
- Browne, Syd - Old New York, 1935 (Folder FF 4)
  Etching, 8 1/16" x 20 1/2"
- Browne, Syd - Along the Harlem River, 1937 (Folder FF 4)
  Etching, 7 3/4" x 9 3/4".
- Bry, Edith - Burned-Out, circa 1939 (Folder FF 6)
  Lithograph, 9" x 13 3/4".
- Chaney, Ruth - Basketball, undated (Folder FF 16)
  Lithograph, 13 1/16" x 10 1/4", WPA.
- Citron, Minna - An Honest Living, 1934 (Folder FF 11)
  Etching, Federal Art Project NYC WPA.
- Cook, Howard Norton - Greetings From The House of Weyhe, 1929 (Folder FF 26)
  Wood engraving.
- Correll, Richard V. - The Eastern Front, 1943 (Folder FF 25)
  Linocut.
- Couard, Alexander P. - Steam Fitters, 1930s (Folder FF 26)
  Etching.
- Dalstrom, Gustof - City Corner, undated (Folder FF 11)
  Aquatint, 3 7/8" x 3 7/8".
- Daniel, Lewis C. - Half-Nelson (Wrestlers), undated (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 13 1/2" x 9 1/2".
- Decker, Albert H. - Empty Lot, 1946 (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 8 3/8" x 10 3/4".
- Dehn, Adolf - Street Scene, 1937 (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 9 1/4" x 12 15/16".
- Dehn, Adolf - Swinging at the Savoy, undated (Folder FF 12)
- Dehnman, Karl - Metropolitan Museum at Night, 1925 (Folder FF 1)
- Dolice, Leon - East 34th Street, undated (Folder FF 1)
- Dolice, Leon - Madison Square Garden, 1922 (Folder FF 1)
- Dwight, Mabel - Buried Treasure, undated (Folder FF 14)
  Lithograph, 12 3/4" x 9 7/8".
- Dwight, Mabel - The Ocean, Coney Island, 1928 (Folder FF 14)
- Dwight, Mabel - Backyard, 1938 (Folder FF 23)
- Eichenberg, Fritz - A.D. 1904, 1936 (Folder FF 24)
  Wood engraving, FAP NYC WPA.
- Farge, Henri - Le Bullwark a Coney Island [Boardwalk, Coney Island], undated (Folder FF 23)
- Farge, Henri - Girl at Coney Island, 1920s (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 7 1/4" x 6 3/4".
- Feinstein, David - Card Players, 1937 (Folder FF 4)
  Lithograph, 13 7/8" x 11 3/4".
- Fife, Mary - The Lovers (1st Stoop), circa 1935 (Folder FF 3)
  Lithograph, 12 3/4" x 13 1/4".
- Freelon, Alan - Number One Broad Street, 1934 (Folder FF 24)
  Aquatint.
- Freeman, Don - The Passing Show [Carriage Driver], undated (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 9 1/8" x 10 1/2".
- Freeman, Don - Box Office, 1934 (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 9 7/8" x 11".
- Friedlander, Isaac - Accordion Player, undated (Folder FF 7)
  Wood engraving, 12 7/16" x 9 3/16".
- Gag, Wanda - Progress, 1936 (Folder FF 2)
  Lithograph, 8 1/16" x 11 3/4".
- Ganso, Emil - New York Rooftops, 1929 (Folder FF 4)
  Lithograph, 17 1/4" x 11 5/8".
- Ganso, Emil - Metropolis, Union Square, 1938 (Folder FF 4)
  Aquatint, 11 3/8" x 14 7/8".
- Geerlings, Gerald Kenneth - Civic Insomnia (New York), 1932 (Folder FF 4)
  Aquatint, 107/8" x 14 3/16".
- Geerlings, Gerald Kenneth - Old Spire, New Towers, undated (Folder FF 4)
  Lithograph, 13 1/6" x 9 1/2".
- Gellert, Hugo - Transformation of Money into Capital, 1933 (Folder FF 1)
- Gellert, Hugo - The Supreme Court (The Swallow in Chancery), 1936 (Folder FF 1)
- Gellert, Hugo - Capital is the Only Fruit of Labor (Lincoln, Politician and Worker), undated (Folder FF 1)
  Lithograph, 14" x 12 3/8".
- Gellert, Hugo - The Distribution of Wealth (The Vacuum), undated (Folder FF 1)
  Lithograph, 13 1/2" x 12".
- Gellert, Hugo - [The Wrench], undated (Folder FF 1)
  Lithograph, 14 1/8" x 12 5/8".
- Gilnsky, Vincent - Coney Island Beach, undated (Folder FF 23)
- Glintenkamp, Henry J. - Floor of Stock Exchange, 1929 (Folder FF 2)
  Wood engraving, 6 3/8" x 4 5/16".
- Goetz, Esther B. - Orchard Street, 1933 (Folder FF 11)
  Etching, 8 7/8" x 6 7/8".
- Gorelick, Boris - Sweat Shop, 1937 (Folder FF 17)
  Lithograph, 11 3/4" x 15 3/8".
- Gottlieb, Harry - Three Lane Traffic, 1938 (Folder FF 17)
  Lithograph, 10 3/8" x 14", WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Grambs, Blanche - Salvation, circa 1936 (Folder FF 1)
  Lithograph, 17 1/2" x 13 3/4".
- Grant, Gordon - [Harbor in Winter], undated (Folder FF 12)
  Lithograph, 8 3/4" x 12".
- Greenberger, Isabelle - Beware of a Dark Young Man, circa 1936 (Folder FF 25)
  Aquatint, WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Greenburg, Samuel - Refugee Family, undated (Folder FF 3)
  Linocut, 12" x 8".
- Greenburg, Samuel - A Breath of Air, 1945 (Folder FF 3)
  Etching, 12 11/16" x 13".
- Gropper, William - Uprooted, undated (Folder FF 7)
  Lithograph, 10 3/8" x 15 9/16".
- Groth, John - Relief, 1938 (Folder FF 6)
  Lithograph, 15 1/4" x 20".
- Hawkins, Basil - Strikers, 1936-1942 (Folder FF 14)
  Etching, 10 3/4" x 7 1/4", WPA.
- Heaslip, William - Spilling the Chute, undated (Folder FF 7)
  Lithograph, 8 7/8" x 11 7/8".
- Hoover, Ellison - Manhattan Midnight, circa 1940 (Folder FF 18)
- Hoover, Ellison - Pulitzer Fountain Evening, undated (Folder FF 18)
- Huntley, Victoria Hutson - To New York, 1933 (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 7 3/4" x 12 1/4".
- Karoly, Andrew - The Builders in N.Y., undated (Folder FF 1)
  Etching, handcolored.
- Kent, Rockwell - And Now Where, 1936 (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 13" x 9 1/4".
- King, Alexander - Game of Skill, undated (Folder FF 16)
  Lithograph, 13 3/4" x 10 15/15", WPA.
- Kopack, Adolph - New York Night Lights, 1931 (Folder FF 24)
- Kruse, Alexander - City Hall Park, undated (Folder FF 13)
  Lithograph, 9 3/8" x 13 1/4".
- Kubinyi, Kalman - Worker, undated (Folder FF 16)
- Kuhler, Otto - Third Avenue "El" at 42nd Street, undated (Folder FF 2)
  Etching, 10 9/16" x 8".
- Lalun, Renee - Having a Beer, undated (Folder FF 13)
  Lithograph, 10 7/8" x 9 1/4".
- Landeck, Armin - Bedford Street, undated (Folder FF 24)
- Landeck, Amin - 14th Cent Skyscrapers, undated (Folder FF 24)
- Leighton, Clare - Loopers, 1942 (Folder FF 11)
- Levy, Israel - Two Women-Bank, 1939-1940 (Folder FF 2)
- Limbach, Russell T. - Reviewing Stand, 1934 (Folder FF 22)
- Lindsey, Richard - Checkers, circa 1940 (Folder FF 6)
  Lithograph, 13 3/4" x 16 15/16".
- Locke, Charles - Bar, undated (Folder FF 2)
  Etching, 6 3/4" x 4 3/4".
- Locke, Charles - Joe's Place, 1935 (Folder FF 2)
  Lithograph, 8 1/2" x 12 3/4".
- Locke, Charles - City Wharves, undated (Folder FF 2)
  Lithograph 8 3/16" x 11 5/16".
- Lubbers, Adrian - Broad Street (20), 1929 (Folder FF 3)
  Lithograph, 16 11/16" x 5 7/8".
- Lubbers, Adrian - Central Park (20), 1929 (Folder FF 3)
  Lithograph, 14 1/2 x 8 3/4".
- Lubbers, Adrian - Central Park Snow Scene, 1930 (Folder FF 26)
- Mack, Harry - Eyes on the Army, 1936-1942 (Folder FF 25)
  Drypoint, WPA Federal Art Project NYC.
- Mandelman, Beatrice - Night Scene, undated (Folder FF 16)
- Marlow, Jack - Relief, 1935-1943 (Folder FF 22)
- McVicker, Jay - Abandoned, circa 1940 (Folder FF 4)
  Lithograph and aquatint, 10 1/2" x 16".
- McWhirter, J. - Judgement, circa 1940 (Folder FF 22)
- Meyerowitz, William - Men in the Park, undated (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 7 13/16 x 9 3/4".
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - St. Thomas New York, undated (Folder FF 7)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Catherine Market, 1903 (Folder FF 8)
  Etching, 9 1/2" x 6 9/16".
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - [Brooklyn Waterfront], undated (Folder FF 8)
  Etching, 9" x 13 1/4".
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Old Toms, undated (Folder FF 8)
  Etching, 9 7/8" x 6 1/4".
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - High Bridge on the Harlem River, 1917 (Folder FF 8)
  Etching, 12 1/2" x 9 3/8".
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Statue of Liberty, undated (Folder FF 8)
  Etching, 6 3/4" x 9 5/8".
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - The Butcher's Shop [Fifth Avenue Market], 1910 (Folder FF 8)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - Porch, Old Customs House, 1905 (Folder FF 8)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - Old Door, Houston Street, 1903 (Folder FF 8)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - The Three Houses, West 14th Street, 1914 (Folder FF 8)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - [Corner House], 1908 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - [Hanging Out the Rugs], 1907 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Emerson's House on Beech Street [Pink House], 1908 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Door, Astor House, 1910 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F.W. - Old Spar Yard in South Street, 1891 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - Driveway, Looking Out 14th Street, 1912 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - Porch, St. Thomas, 1910 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - The Toy Shop, 1903 (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - Castle Clinton and the Battery, undated (Folder FF 9)
- Mielatz, Charles F. W. - The Lock, Mott Haven Canal, 1891 (Folder FF 9)
- Miller, Benjamin - The City (Christ in Times Square), 1930 (Folder FF 2)
  Woodcut, 11 7/8" x 8".
- Mockel, Henry R. - Franklin Square, N.Y., undated (Folder FF 22)
- Murphy, Alice Harold - Umbrellas, 1937 (Folder FF 7)
  Lithograph, 9 1/2" x 12 13/16".
- Myers, Jerome - [Parents and children in the park], undated (Folder FF 26)
  Etching and drypoint.
- Mygate, Robertson K. - [Tenements with laundry], undated (Folder FF 3)
  Etching, 11 5/16" x 8 3/16".
- Nooney, Ann - Amusement Park, undated (Folder FF 14)
- Olds, Elizabeth - Mrs. Manchester's Program for Homeless Men, 1936 (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 10" x 15 1/8".
- Olds, Elizabeth - I Make Steel, undated (Folder FF 17)
  Lithograph, 17 1/2" x 13 3/4", WPA.
- Partridge, Roi - 43 Wall Street, 1914 (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 7 9/16" x 10 1/16".
- Paull, Grace - Winter Sunday in Washington Square, 1947 (Folder FF 21)
- Pearson, Ralph M. - Toilers of the City, circa 1915 (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 13 7/8" x 11 3/4".
- Penny, James - Thompson's, 1933 (Folder FF 6)
  Lithograph, 12 7/16" x 17".
- Penny, James - Bar, circa 1932 (Folder FF 6)
- Peterson, Martin - [East River Coal Depot], circa 1930 (Folder FF 21)
- Pinto, Salvator - The Steel Bucket, undated (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 7 3/4" x 9 5/8".
- Potter, Albert - East Side, New York, circa 1935 (Folder FF 12)
  Linocut, 8" x 10".
- Raboy, Mac - Migrant Workers, circa 1937 (Folder FF 16)
- Rein, Harry - Under the El, undated (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 13 1/4" x 10".
- Rein, Harry - Idols, undated (Folder FF 5)
- Reisman, Philip - Butcher Shop, undated (Folder FF 11)
  Etching, 4 13/16" x 5 7/8".
- Rico, Donato - Homecoming, undated (Folder FF 14)
  Wood engraving, 8 1/2" x 6 1/2".
- Rico, Donato - Home Relief Bureau, circa 1937 (Folder FF 14)
  Lithograph, 16 3/8" x 13 3/8".
- Rico, Donato - End of Day, 1935-1937 (Folder FF 14)
- Rico, Donato - Blast Furnace Brooklyn NY, 1939 (Folder FF 19)
- Rico, Donato - Signs of the City, undated (Folder FF 19)
- Rico, Donato - Conversation Piece, 1935-1943 (Folder FF 19)
- Roth, Ernest David - Queensboro Bridge-Manhattan, 1905 (Folder FF 18)
- Roth, Ernest David - Jeanette Park-South Street and Coenties Slip, 1948 (Folder FF 18)
- Roth, Ernest David - Angles of NY (Union Square), 1945 (Folder FF 4)
- Ruch, Roslyn - Sea Beach Express, undated (Folder FF 11)
- Shrag, Karl - Persecution, 1940 (Folder FF 5)
  Etching/aquatint, 11 15/16 x 6 11/16.
- Simon, T.F. - New York Stock Exchange, 1927 (Folder FF 27)
  Color soft ground and aquatint.
- Skolfield, Raymond - The Street Hawkers, 1936 (Folder FF 17)
- Sloan, John - Fifth Avenue Critics, 1905 (Folder FF 11)
  Etching, 4 1/2" x 6 11/16".
- Soifer, Howard - Ninth Street, 1937 (Folder FF 21)
- Soyer, Raphael - Springtime, 1938 (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 14" x 17 1/4".
- Soyer, Raphael - Waterfront Scene, 1934 (Folder FF 5)
  Lithograph, 8 3/4" x 13 1/4".
- Steinberg, Nathaniel P. - The Stoker, circa 1933 (Folder FF 13)
  Drypoint, 7 3/8" x 8 7/8".
- Sternberg, Harry - Warming Up the Power Station, circa 1930 (Folder FF 12)
  Etching and aquatint, 9 3/4" x 11 3/4".
- Trovato, Joseph S. - Notice from the Draft Board, 1943 (Folder FF 2)
  Woodcut, 14" x 11 3/8".
- Trovato, Joseph S. - Gas Station, undated (Folder FF 2)
  Woodcut, 8 1/8" x 11".
- Uhl, K. - Night Before November 3, undated (Folder FF 5)
- Unknown - [Having a Drink], undated (Folder FF 3)
  Lithograph and aquatint, 9 3/4" x 9 7/8".
- Van Notti, Henry - New York-Vesey and West Streets, undated (Folder FF 4)
  Color etching, 9 13/16" x 11 9/16".
- Wahl, Theodore - Midtown Tunnel, 1934 (Folder FF 22)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly I: The Lovers, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
  Mezzotint, 8" x 4 13/16".
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly II: Old Men, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly III: Dogs of War, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly IV: Medicos, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly V: Pettifoggers (Lawyers), 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly VI: Preachers, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly VII: Pedagogues, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly VIII: Courtiers, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly IX: Judges, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
- Ward, Lynd Kendall - In Praise of Folly X: Churchmen, 1943 (Folder FF 10)
  Mezzotint, 8" x 4" 13/16".
- Webb, A.J. - Damaged Goods, 1936-37 (Folder FF 5)
  Etching and drypoint, 9 11/16" x 8 11/16".
- Webb, A.J. - Driftwood, undated (Folder FF 5)
  Etching, 10 7/8" x 9 7/8", WPA.
- Webb, A.J. - Poor Fish, circa 1937 (Folder FF 21)
- Weller, Paul - Harvest Hands, undated (Folder FF 14)
  Lithograph, 11" x 17", WPA.
- Weller, Paul - Freight, 1936-1942 (Folder FF 14)
  Lithograph, 12 1/2" x 9 5/8", WPA
- White, Charles Henry - [Lower New York], 1905 (Folder FF 12)
  Etching, 4 15/16" x 6".
- Wickey, Harry Newman - 9th Avenue, circa 1920 (Folder FF 22)
- Wickey, Harry Newman - Sleeping Under the Bridge, 1923 (Folder FF 13)
  Etching, 7 13/16" x 9 3/4".
- Williams, Mildred Emerson - Winter, Central Park, 1935-1941 (Folder FF 16)
  Lithograph, WPA Federal Arts Project NYC.
- Witonsky, Ted - Dispute, undated (Folder FF 16)
  Etching, 4 15/16" x 6", WPA.
- Young, Mahonri Mackintosh - Tearing Down the Old Grand Central, circa 1913 (Folder FF 1)
- Zeigler, Henry - Play Safe!, undated (Folder FF 11)
  Etching and drypoint, 8 13/16" x 7 1/8".
- Zeigler, Henry - When Greek Meets Greek, undated (Folder FF 11)